[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phobia is defined as fear of thunder?", "correct_answer": "Ceraunophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Coimetrophobia", "Chronomentrophobia", "Claustrophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the nanny who must take care of the two children of Richard and Susan in the movie Babel?", "correct_answer": "Amelia", "incorrect_answers": ["Maria", "Rosana", "Luz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first successful artificial satellite?", "correct_answer": "Sputnik 1", "incorrect_answers": ["Explorer", "None of these", "Discoverer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The male protagonist of Sleepless in Seattle and his friend, Greg, cry when seeing this movie.", "correct_answer": "The Dirty Dozen", "incorrect_answers": ["Captains Courageous", "Casablanca", "All Quiet on the Western Front"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rachel Green, Jennifer Anistons character in Friends, has two sisters. One of them is played by Christina Allpegate. Who plays the other sister?", "correct_answer": "Reese Witherspoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Scarlett Johansson", "Sarah Michelle Gellar", "Lindsay Lohan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This  very successful rock group appeared in an episode of Will and Grace.", "correct_answer": "Hall and Oates", "incorrect_answers": ["Genesis", "Bon Jovi", "The Bangles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 3:10 to Yuma, what is Ben Wades justification for shooting Tommy Darden?", "correct_answer": "He put the whole gang at risk.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was an undercover Pinkerton.", "He was a thief.", "He insulted his mother."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ireland and Nigeria are considered to be among the countries with most adults, regularly attending church services. The citizens of one of this country also go to church regularly.", "correct_answer": "Poland", "incorrect_answers": ["Finland", "Russia", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Mitchies mom in the movie Camp Rock?", "correct_answer": "Connie", "incorrect_answers": ["Caitlyn", "Tess", "Ella"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name Obi Wan Kenobis mentor who died in the first Star Wars movie duelling Darth Maul.", "correct_answer": "Qui Gon Jin", "incorrect_answers": ["Anakan Skywalker", "Luke Skywalker", "Yoda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning actor starred in the 1967 comedy movie The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "Dustin Hoffman", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert De Niro", "All of these", "Jack Nicholson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these dinosaurs was carnivorous?", "correct_answer": "Eoraptor", "incorrect_answers": ["Diplodocus", "Maiasaura", "Triceratops"]}]